Guide to the George Mason University Libraries records, 1949-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 7: Library departments and services, 1959-2008
  - Subseries 7.8: Special Collections and Archives (SC&A), 1950-2007
    - Educational film channel, 2001 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Educational film channel, Federal Theatre Project proposal, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Encapsulation project of Federal Theatre Project paper billboards and posters, 1983 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Equipment for library III, 1981-1982 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Finding aids sample preliminary pages, 1997 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Fitzgerald papers, 1979 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Folklore center, 1977-1978 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Forms for boxes, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Forms, deed of gift, 1976 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Forms, equipment inventory, circa 1980s (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Forms, folder forms, circa 1980s (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Forms, Free, adult, uncensored form letter, circa 1980s (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - Forms, letters templates for the Federal Theatre Project, circa 1970s (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Forms, librarians' evaluation, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 177, Folder 15)
    - Forms, outdated forms, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 177, Folder 16)
    - Friends of library (Agronsky reception and exhibits), 1980 (Box 177, Folder 17)
    - Friends of the library, 1980-1982 (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - GMU Foundation, 1979-1981 (Box 177, Folder 19)
    - George C. Harris slide presentation (Mrs. Snowden Conkey), 1979 (Box 177, Folder 20)
    - General Special Collections information, 1979 (Box 177, Folder 21)
    - General Special Collections information, 1979 (Box 177, Folder 22)
    - General Special Collections information, 1995-1996 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - General Special Collections information, 2003 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Grant application, American Symphony Orchestra League (ASOL), 1979 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Grant application, Atkins (Ollie), 1979 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Grant application, documents to the people, 1979 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Grants, facilities, 1979 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Grants, general information, 1977-1979 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Grant, #RC-23973-76-510 final report copy, 1979 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Grant, NEH #RC-23973-76-510 final report, 1979 April (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Grant, NEH #RC-34806-78-1264 final report, 1978 October 1-1979 May 31 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Grant, NEH applications, 1974-1979 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Grant, NEH grant correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Grant, NEH grant letters of support, 1975-1979 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Grant, NEH planning grant proposal, 1979 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Grant, NEH RV-20004-81-0896 preservation management conference, 1981 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Grant, PAR grant application, 1979 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Grant, Rockefeller grant, 1976-1980 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Grant, Virginia endowment for the arts and public policy, 1976 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Grants proposals and National Archives public education program proposal, 1976 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Grants, AAUW graduate fellowships, circa 1975 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - Grants applied for, 1975-1978 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - Grant, Meyer grant, framing exhibit materials, 1979 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Grant, Meyer grant, high school outreach, 1979 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - Grant, NEA information, 1976-1978 (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - Grant, puppetry exhibit proposal, 1980 (Box 179, Folder 13)
    - Guides to collections of research materials in the performing arts, 1980 (Box 179, Folder 14)
      Brochures
    - History project, Dr. McFarlane, 1986 (Box 179, Folder 15)
    - Library of Congress calendars and cards, 1985-1986 (Box 179, Folder 16)
    - Meetings of activity heads, 1980-1981 (Box 179, Folder 17)
    - Meetings of activity heads, 1981-1982 (Box 179, Folder 18)
    - Meeting, Special Collections, 1996 January 16 (Box 179, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 179, Folder 20)
    - Monthly report notes, 1979-1985 (Box 179, Folder 21)
    - Monthly reports, 1985 (Box 179, Folder 22)
    - Annual reports, 2000-2002 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Annual reports, 2004 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - RCMS biennial report, 1998-2000 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Biannual report draft, 1998-2000 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Biennial report, 2000-2002 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Biennial report, 2002 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Biennial report, 2003-2005 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Most current work, 1976-1981 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Things that have been done, 1981 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Monthly reports, 1981 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Monthly reports, 1983-1992 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Monthly reports, 1980-1983 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Monthly reports, 1984-1998 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Monthly reports, 1992-1997 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Monthly reports, 2000-2001 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Monthly reports, 2001 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Monthly reports, 2001-2002 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Monthly reports, 2002-2003 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Statistics and summaries of activities, 1994-2004 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Counters, 1997-2000 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Monthly statistics (raw data), 2006-2007 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Circulation desk statistics, 2007 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Staff activity log, undated (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - NEH summer institute, 2005-2006 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Oral history website, 1999 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Edwin Meese III, 2006 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Oral history pamphlet, 2006 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Simon interview, 2007 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - NOVA oral history guide and index copy 2, undated (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Personnel, graduate assistantships, 1981 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Personnel, in-house memorandums, 1975-1982 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Personnel, January internship program, 1977-1978 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Personnel, job descriptions, 1979-1981 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Personnel, speaking engagements by staff for the Federal Theatre Project, 1977 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Personnel, student volunteer announcement, 1981 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Personnel, Walsh, Elizabeth D. memorial, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Policies and procedures, activities, 1981-1982 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Policies and procedures, bookplates, 2004 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Policies and procedures, cataloging, 1980-1981 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Policies and procedures, cataloging, 1992-2000 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Policies and procedures, circulation, 1981-1982 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, 1981-1982 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, 1980 (Box 207, Folder 8)
      "A donor's guide" brochure
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, accessions, 1975 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, acquisitions, 1979-1981 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, acquisitions, circa 1980 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, acquisitions, 2003 (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, acquisitions, 2003 (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, books used and rare, 1999 (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, bookseller information, 2001-2004 (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, collecting guidelines, 2001-2005 (Box 207, Folder 16)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, collection guidelines for archives, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 17)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, donor guidelines, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 18)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, faculty papers, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 19)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, guidelines for inclusion of materials in Special Collections, 1980 (Box 207, Folder 20)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, microforms, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 21)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, missing items, 2002-2003 (Box 207, Folder 22)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development policy, circa 1981 (Box 207, Folder 23)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development policy, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 24)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, transferal of Special Collections items, 2005 (Box 207, Folder 25)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development, vendors, 2004-2005 (Box 207, Folder 26)
    - Policies and procedures, collection development and management, 2001-2004 (Box 207, Folder 27)
    - Policies and procedures, conservation, 1981-1982 (Box 207, Folder 28)
      Technical bulletin
    - Policies and procedures, costume designs, undated (Box 207, Folder 29)
    - Policies and procedures, emergencies, disaster and preparedness plans, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 30)
    - Policies and procedures, exhibits, circa 1980 (Box 207, Folder 31)
    - Policies and procedures, fumigation, 1980-1982 (Box 207, Folder 32)
    - Policies and procedures, fumigation, African art collection, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 33)
    - Policies and procedures, fumigation, Mann, Federal Theatre Project collections, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 34)
    - Policies and procedures, fumigation, Ross collection, 1981 (Box 207, Folder 35)
    - Policies and procedures, fumigation, Warburton materials, 1981 (Box 207, Folder 36)
    - Policies and procedures, Librarians' handbook, 1982 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Policies and procedures, libraries, 1981 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Policies and procedures, library code of Virginia, circa 1980 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Policies and procedures, Library of Congress copyright, 2000 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Policies and procedures, Library of Congress lending materials, 1974 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Policies and procedures, Library of Congress loan policy, 1977-1980 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Policies and procedures, Library of Congress exhibit coordination policies and regulations, 1981 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Policies and procedures, library leave and pay procedures, 1999 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Policies and procedures, licensing issues and copyright, 2004-2006 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Policies and procedures, licensing information, 2003 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Policies and procedures, management by objectives, 1980-1981 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Policies and procedures, oral history policies, 1976 (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Policies and procedures, photocopying procedures, 1980 (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Policies and procedures, archives policy statement, 1982 (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Policies and procedures, 1980-1981 (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - Policies and procedures manual, circa 1980s (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - Policies and procedures manual, 1999 (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - Preservation policies, fumigation process and hazards, 1982 (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - Preservation policies, insurance, 1979-1982 (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - Preservation policies, vacufume 18 specifications, 1982 (Box 181, Folder 20)
    - Research policies, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Research policies, circa 1980 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Procedures and goals, 1978-1979 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Processing services, acquisitions, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Processing services, Bryn Mawr songbook, 1982 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Processing services, cataloging, 1981 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Processing services, cataloging playscripts, circa 1980 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Processing services, supplies, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Projects, 1997-2000 (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Projects, Bib-win CD-Rom, undated (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Projects, bibliography for Eames Smith, circa 2000s (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Projects, C-Span Booknotes, 2005 (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Projects, catalogue project (Procite), 2000 (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - Projects, council of planning librarians archives, 2005 (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Projects, digital imaging project, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - Projects, digital imaging project, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 13)
      Correspondence and notes
    - Projects, history of photography, 2000 (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - Projects, history of science and technology, R. Rosenzweig, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 15)
    - Projects, history of science and technology, R. Rosenzweig, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - Projects, internship information, 2000 (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - Projects, internship portfolio, 2000 (Box 182, Folder 18)
    - Projects, Jamestown books in OPAC (includes Helm collection books), 2006 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Projcets, Jamestown fiction, 2003 (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - Projects, Jennifer's updates (web), 2002 (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Projects, Leslie Smith (NCC), 2000 (Box 182, Folder 19)
    - Projects, Lloyd Reitnaeur, 2002 (Box 206, Folder 16)
    - Projects, Planned Community Archives (PCA) founders web site, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 21)
    - Projects, play projects, undated (Box 206, Folder 17)
    - Projects, Pocahontas bibliography, 2004 (Box 206, Folder 18)
    - Projects, Raphe Homer, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - Projects, researching rare books, 2004 (Box 206, Folder 19)
    - Projects, student research projects, 2000 (Box 182, Folder 22)
    - Projects, George Mason books, 2001-2003 (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - Projects, handouts from workshops, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 24)
    - Projects, Wanda's project, 1995 (Box 182, Folder 25)
    - Publicity, The Washington Post arts, 2000 December 12 (Box 182, Folder 26)
    - Re-allocation of resources, 1980-1981 (Box 182, Folder 27)
    - Reconfiguring and renovation, 2005 (Box 182, Folder 28)
    - Records management storage, 1982-1986 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Records retention, 1979-1986 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Research center, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Security, access to Special Collections, 1980-1981 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Services, public, community outreach program, 1978-1979 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Service requests, new student orientation, 1979-1981 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Service requests, tours, 1979-1982 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Shelving, circa 2000s (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Space business archives, possible donation, 1991 (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Thomas Balch library, Leesburg, VA, Claude Moore research, circa 2004 (Box 183, Folder 10)
      Pamphlets and notes
    - University of Virginia literature, 1997-2005 (Box 183, Folder 11)
      Other special collections brochures and information
    - University of Virginia literature, 1989-2000s (Box 183, Folder 12)
- Series 8: Administrative files, 1958-2001
  This series is divided into three subseries; gifts, grants, and personnel. Arranged alphabetically, then chronologically.
  - Subseries 8.1: Gifts, 1958-1989
    Contains acknowledgements of gifts received by the library.
    - Administration, Barager, Jose R., 1979 (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Administration, Cannavale, Frank J. Jr. memorial book fund, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - Administration, Cornelsen, Phyllis memorial, 1974-1976 (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Administration, Dodge-Jones endowment, 1974-1975 (Box 183, Folder 16)
    - Administration, Dykstra, Nellie Schippers memorial book fund, 1975 (Box 183, Folder 17)
    - Administration, Jewish Publication Society of America (Muriel and Phillip Berman gift), 1976-1977 (Box 183, Folder 18)
    - Administration, Lahr Memorial Trust Fund, 1974-1977 (Box 183, Folder 19)
    - Administration, Wilkins, John, circa 1970s (Box 183, Folder 20)
    - Biology Foundation Fund, 1983 (Box 183, Folder 21)
    - Hatch, Winslow, 1980-1981 (Box 183, Folder 22)
    - The Japajag foundation, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 23)
    - Letters of appreciation, 1958-1968 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Letters of appreciation, 1958-1969 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Letters of appreciation, 1969-1972 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Letters of appreciation, 1969-1972 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Letters of appreciation, 1973 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Letters of appreciation, 1974 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Letters of appreciation, 1975 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Letters of appreciation, 1976 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Letters of appreciation, 1977 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - University development, 1978-1989 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 8.2: Grants, 1966-1993
    Includes grant correspondence, proposals, and requests.
    - 1989-1992 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - $5000 grant, 1966 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Applications for federal grants, 1966-1969 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Application for grants, 1977 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Basic grants for libraries, 1966 (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Challenge, Northern Virginia gerontology, 1977-1978 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - College library resources title II (Gladstone file), 1979 (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Center and arts grants, 1978-1979 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Discussion topics, 1977 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Federal grant applications, 1970-1973 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Federal grant applications, 1974-1982 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Federal Theatre Project, performing arts resources publication (Cornell), 1980 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Financial (Greene) NEH grant #5-22024 and GMU 1-41900, 1979 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Gerontology, 1978 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Gerontology, 1978 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - Gerontology proposal, title IV, A, courses, 1978-1979 (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - Gerontology proposal, working papers, 1978 (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Gerontology vitaes, 1978 (Box 186, Folder 13)
    - Grant application working file, 1993 (Box 186, Folder 14)
    - Grant administration, 1985-1992 (Box 186, Folder 15)
    - Grant proposals, Office for Research, 1991-1993 (Box 186, Folder 16)
    - Instructions on how to apply for grants, 1977-1978 (Box 186, Folder 17)
    - Japan Foundation, 1991-1993 (Box 186, Folder 18)
    - Library demonstration, 1978-1979 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Letters of authorization, 1979 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, how to get grants, circa 1970s (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Museum at GMU grant information, 1978-1980 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Other videotape equipment, 1979 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Photography NEA, 1978-1979 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Proposal SCHEV, 1992-1993 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Proposal SCHEV, 1993 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Proposal SCHEV title II A, 1993 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Department of education title II, 1981-1982 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Title II D, 1988 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Requests, 1976-1981 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Requests, 1976-1981 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Sharing on-line databases code 5_22522, 1984 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - State librarian Haynes, 1983-1984 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - VFH miscellaneous information, 1979-1980 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Virginia state library, government document for all people, 1989-1991 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - VFH pamphlets, 1978-1979 (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - VFHPP mail lists, circa 1979 (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - Women's action alliance, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 8.3: Personnel, 1964-1995
    Includes faculty information, organization charts, personnel procedures and information on volunteer programs.
    - Affirmative action recruitment, 1977-1981 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative action resources person (AARP), 1984 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Applying flextime in Fenwick Library proposal, 1984 December 19 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Department liaisons, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Faculty and instructors, 1961-1964 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Faculty lists, 1964-1965, 1969-1980 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Faculty of the University Libraries, 1970s-1980s (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Faculty vita system, 1985 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Faculty workloads, overloads, 1975 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Farewell party for Ruth Kifer, 2005 September 12 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Follow-up identification system, 1974-1976 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Historic organization, 1981-1984 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - Human resources, 1990-1995 (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Library staff, 1973 (Box 189, Folder 14)
    - New position requests, 1989-1990 (Box 189, Folder 15)
    - OAR, prescriptive sentencing program, 1986 (Box 189, Folder 16)
    - Organization chart, 1984 (Box 189, Folder 17)
    - Organization chart Fenwick Library, 1987-1988 (Box 189, Folder 18)
    - Organization charts, other libraries, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 19)
    - Library organizational, 1975 (Box 189, Folder 20)
    - Library positions, 1975 (Box 189, Folder 21)
    - Library reorganization, 1980-1983 (Box 189, Folder 22)
    - Library school interns, 1986 February 19 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Pay scales of librarians at the University of Virginia, 1960s (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Performance appraisal, 1993 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Personnel general information, hiring, inclement weather plan, 1980-1981 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Personnel procedures, 1981-1982 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Position description information, undated (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Reclass information, 1989 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Ruth Kerns retirement, 1993 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Salary data, 1985 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Special announcement, staff development survey, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Staff development training, 1987-1989 (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - Staff lists, 1988 (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - Staffing the library, 1975-1977 (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Staff assistant forms, 1986 (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - Telesec, 1989 (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - University list, distribution, 1979 (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Virginia libraries staff comparison, circa 1981 (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - Volunteer papers (blank), 1987 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Volunteer program, 1983-1984 (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - Volunteer program publications, 1982-1984 (Box 190, Folder 20)
      Information on library volunteer programs
    - Requests for volunteers, 1984 (Box 190, Folder 21)
    - Volunteers, 1982-1983 (Box 190, Folder 22)
    - Volunteers public relations, 1983 (Box 190, Folder 23)
    - Volunteers questionnaires, 1983 (Box 190, Folder 24)
    - Volunteers, Washington urban league, 1984 (Box 190, Folder 25)
    - Work transition act (Human resources), 1995 (Box 190, Folder 26)
- Series 9: Miscellaneous, 1949-2001
  This series includes miscellaneous correspondence, memorandums, statistics, policies and brochures.
  - Anne M. Hughes assistant librarian, 1965 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Arlington Campus Library, 2000-2009 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Brochures, Prolibris, Council of Higher Education, 1989-1993 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Certificate of appreciation from the Office of Partnerships Adopt-A-Family initiative, 2001 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Fine arts loan agreement form (blank), 1990 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Logos for Fenwick Library, undated (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous memorandums and reports, 1967-1993 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous memorandums and meetings, 1949-1988 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous notes, circulation letter, SACS email, 1994 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous statistics and policies, 1980 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - University equity office and Dr. Ingram, 1992-1995 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - University library programs, 1980s-1990s (Box 192, Folder 6)
- Series 10: Photographs, audiovisual, artifacts 1967-1999
  This series includes photographs, audiovisual materials such as VHS and audio cassette tapes, and artifacts including Mason related buttons.